(UPBEAT MUSIC)
(ROOSTER CROWS)
(KATHY YELLS)
- FRIDAY!
- HEY KATHY!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- LISTEN, I JUST
WANT TO THANK YOU FOR
LITERALLY THE BEST
PARTY OF ALL TIME.
IT WAS ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT
ANYONE SAYS ABOUT YOU,
YOU'RE ACTUALLY REALLY COOL.
BEST PARTY EVER WOO!
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
♪ THERE'S A STRANGER IN MY BED ♪
♪ THERE'S A POUNDING
IN MY HEAD ♪
♪ GLITTER ALL OVER THE ROOM ♪
♪ PINK FLAMINGOS IN THE POOL ♪
♪ I SMELL LIKE A MINIBAR ♪
♪ DJ'S PASSED OUT IN THE YARD ♪
♪ BARBIES ON THE BARBECUE ♪
♪ THIS A HICKEY OR A BRUISE ♪
♪ PICTURES OF LAST
NIGHT ENDED UP ONLINE ♪
♪ I'M SCREWED, OH WELL ♪
♪ IT'S A BLACKED OUT BLUR,
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE IT RULED ♪
♪ DAMN ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE DANCED ON TABLETOPS ♪
♪ AND WE TOOK TOO MANY SHOTS ♪
♪ THINK WE KISSED,
BUT I FORGOT ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE MAXED
OUR CREDIT CARDS ♪
♪ AND GOT KICKED
OUT OF THE BAR ♪
♪ SO WE HIT THE BOULEVARD ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ WE WENT STREAKING
IN THE PARK ♪
♪ SKINNY DIPPING IN THE DARK ♪
♪ THEN HAD A MENAGE A TROIS ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, I THINK
WE BROKE THE LAW ♪
♪ ALWAYS SAY WE'RE
GONNA STOP, WHOA ♪
♪ THIS FRIDAY NIGHT,
DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ BUT THIS FRIDAY
NIGHT, DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ TRYING TO CONNECT THE DOTS ♪
♪ DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO TELL MY BOSS ♪
♪ THINK THE CITY TOWED MY CAR ♪
♪ CHANDELIER IS ON THE FLOOR ♪
♪ RIPPED MY FAVORITE
PARTY DRESS ♪
♪ WARRANT'S OUT FOR MY ARREST ♪
♪ THINK I NEED A GINGER ALE ♪
♪ THAT WAS SUCH AN EPIC FAIL ♪
♪ PICTURES OF LAST
NIGHT ENDED UP ONLINE ♪
♪ I'M SCREWED, OH, WELL ♪
♪ IT'S A BLACKED OUT BLUR,
BUT I'M PRETTY SURE IT RULED ♪
♪ DAMN ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE DANCED ON TABLETOPS ♪
♪ AND WE TOOK TOO MANY SHOTS ♪
♪ THINK WE KISSED,
BUT I FORGOT ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE MAXED
OUR CREDIT CARDS ♪
♪ AND GOT KICKED
OUT OF THE BAR ♪
♪ SO WE HIT THE BOULEVARD ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ WE WENT STREAKING
IN THE PARK ♪
♪ SKINNY DIPPING IN THE DARK ♪
♪ THEN HAD A MENAGE A TROIS ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, I THINK
WE BROKE THE LAW ♪
♪ ALWAYS SAY WE'RE
GONNA STOP, WHOA ♪
♪ THIS FRIDAY NIGHT,
DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
♪ THIS FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
(GROUP CHEERING)
♪ TGIF, TGIF, TGIF,
TGIF, TGIF, TGIF, TGIF ♪
♪♪♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE DANCED ON TABLETOPS ♪
♪ AND WE TOOK TOO MANY SHOTS ♪
♪ THINK WE KISSED,
BUT I FORGOT ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, WE MAXED
OUR CREDIT CARDS ♪
♪ AND GOT KICKED
OUT OF THE BAR ♪
♪ SO WE HIT THE BOULEVARD ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ WE WENT STREAKING
IN THE PARK ♪
♪ SKINNY DIPPING IN THE DARK ♪
♪ THEN HAD A MENAGE A TROIS ♪
♪ LAST FRIDAY NIGHT ♪
♪ YEAH, I THINK
WE BROKE THE LAW ♪
♪ ALWAYS SAY WE'RE
GONNA STOP, WHOA ♪
♪ BUT THIS FRIDAY
NIGHT, DO IT ALL AGAIN ♪
- WHAT DO YOU THINK THIS
EGG WAS DOING ON THE--
- I HAVE NO IDEA.
- KATHY BETH TERRY, WHAT
HAPPENED TO YOUR ROOM?
- MOM, DAD!
- WHY IS THERE SOME
LOST BOY IN YOUR BED?
- I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
I JUST WOKE UP AND MY SOLAR
SYSTEM WAS OFF OF THE POST!
- OH MY GOODNESS.
SO IRRESPONSIBLE.
- AND WHAT'S UNCLE KENNY
DOING ON THE COUCH?
- I DIDN'T DO IT,
IT WAS REBECCA.
SHE HAD A PARTY.
- NO, REBECCA BLACK
IS A NICE GIRL.
- YEAH, I DON'T THINK SHE
WOULD'VE STARTED THIS HONEY.
- WHY ARE YOU HOME SO
EARLY FROM THE CONVENTION?
- WELL, I GOT SOME CRAZY
TEXTS FROM UNCLE KENNY
WHO SAID HE WAS GOING TO
START PLAYING THE SAX AGAIN.
- WE HAD TO GET HOME RIGHT AWAY
TO SEE WHAT THAT WAS ALL ABOUT.
- CAN'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
- I LOVE YOU GUYS,
BUT UNCLE KENNY TOLD ME YOU
USED TO BE FUN ON FRIDAY.
- KITTY CAT.
WE INVENTED FRIDAYS.
- I NEED TO SLEEP IT OFF.
- GOODNIGHT HONEY.
(UPBEAT MUSIC)
- WHO KNEW YOUR
UNCLE WAS KENNY G?
RIGHTEOUS, MAN!
BEST PARTY EVER, WOO!
- WHEN YOUR MOM AND I WERE
YOUNG, WE, WE USED TO PARTY,
YOU KNOW.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO YOUR
DIORAMA OF THE SOLAR SYSTEM
THAT YOU WORKED SO HARD ON?
- YOU KNOW, SLEEP ALL
DAY PARTY ALL NIGHT.
THAT WAS OUR MOTTO, RIGHT?
- SOMETHING LIKE THAT, RIGHT.
- ALL THAT KIND.
HONEY, LET'S GO HAVE
OUR OWN FRIDAY NIGHT.
- IT WAS AWESOME, MOM!
KENNY WAS AWESOME!
OH MY GOD, HE'S SO HOT.
(KATHY YELLS)